sundiatapost.com 2019-05-17

# Privacy Policy – SundiataPost

We’ve created this privacy policy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of our customers.

By using our website, mobile and tablet applications and any other Leo Africanus Ltd service, you are consenting and agreeing to the practices outlined in this statement.

Leo Africanus Ltd will always handle information in compliance with the Constitution of the Federal Republic of Nigeria and any Guidelines or regulations on data protection as may be issued by the Nigeria Communication Commission (NCC).

Collection of data and use of your personal information

We collect your data and personal information in the following ways:

On our website when you use the ‘Contact us’ forms for an enquiry  
When you download our mobile and web apps or subscribe to our email newsletters  
We use your data and personal information in the following ways:

To improve our website, prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our website and enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.  
To provide you with requested information or correspondence, such as a SundiataPOST Directory or a response from us to an enquiry made by you.  
To send you details of your new account details or login information – usually via email.  
To contact you in the event of changes to terms and conditions of orders, booking or this privacy policy.  
With your permission, your contact details may be used to supply information to you by telephone, email or post, about our company. and to send you occasional promotional material, such as information about special offers which we think you might find valuable. If you do not agree to receive this information, you may opt out from receiving future information at any time.  
We may also provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third parties but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.  
We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. This ensures that the quality of data we have on your account(s) is maintained properly.  
Non-disclosure to third parties

The information and data we collect is important for Leo Africanus Ltd and we would not want to share this anyone else. Unless we have your express consent, we will never disclose, rent, trade or sell your personal data to any third parties for their marketing or mailing purposes.

In the event that Leo Africanus Ltd or any part of its business is sold to or integrated with another business, Leo Africanus Ltd may disclose your personal information to the new owners (and their professional advisers on the transaction) to be used by the new owners and their group of companies in the same ways as set out in this Privacy Policy, including to continue providing you with the same services and marketing information services as are currently provided by Leo Africanus Ltd.

Credit or debit card data is never viewed or disclosed to anyone, ever.

Cookies

The SundiataPOST Website uses cookies and tags. A cookie is a small file that can be stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive and allows the browser to pass small amounts of information to a web server. Tags are transparent graphic files that appear on web pages that collect anonymous information about usage of the web pages.

The SundiataPOST uses its own cookies and tags as well as those from third parties to allow us to do a number of things that improve your website experience. They are used to compile anonymous statistics related to the use of the website or actions that you may take whilst visiting the website. They can also be used to ensure the website works efficiently or by third parties to present you with appropriate offers and advertising as you view other sites on the internet.

Whilst cookies/tags may identify you as a user of the website, your personal details are not stored or used to individually identify you and the cookie/tag cannot access or store any personal information which you have not provided to the website during your visit. They are also not able to put malicious software or viruses on your computer or change the operation of your equipment.

Leo Africanus Ltd uses cookies/tags to enable the smooth operation of the SundiataPOST website, such as the use of the basket function or to automatically log you in when you visit (with your permission). We also use cookies/tags to monitor website visits and actions to understand the performance of the website and continuously look for places to improve your website experience.

Our marketing/advertising partners also use cookies and tags to monitor the performance of our advertising and to serve appropriate advertisements to you on other websites. We will never share any personal information about you with these third parties and the cookies and tags used maintain your anonymity.

You can usually change your browser’s settings so that it will not accept cookies, although this may restrict some website functionality. You may also manage the cookies on your browser using the security or privacy settings. Usually the browser help function will provide you with instructions on how to manage your settings. Removing cookies is something that can be done at any time but unless permanently disallowed they will be re-applied next time you visit the website.

Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings.

Security of your information

We follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given us. This is to prevent unauthorised access or unlawful processing of your personal information. For additional peace of mind, credit card details are not recorded on the SundiataPOST Website when making an order.

Your consent

By using our website you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information by us in the manner set out in this privacy policy. Should we change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this website so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use and under what circumstances we disclose it.
